{
  "models": [
    {
      "id": 1607392319,
      "name": "Basic",
      "cloze": false,
      "fields": [
        {
          "name": "Front"
        },
        {
          "name": "Back"
        }
      ],
      "cards": [
        {
          "name": "Card 1",
          "front": "{{Front}}",
          "back": "{{FrontSide}}<hr>{{Back}}"
        }
      ],
      "styles": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 1607392320,
      "name": "Basic (and reversed card)",
      "cloze": false,
      "fields": [
        {
          "name": "Front"
        },
        {
          "name": "Back"
        }
      ],
      "cards": [
        {
          "name": "Card 1",
          "front": "{{Front}}",
          "back": "{{FrontSide}}<hr>{{Back}}"
        },
        {
          "name": "Card 2",
          "front": "{{Back}}",
          "back": "{{FrontSide}}<hr>{{Front}}"
        }
      ],
      "styles": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 1607392321,
      "name": "Basic (optional reversed card)",
      "cloze": false,
      "fields": [
        {
          "name": "Front"
        },
        {
          "name": "Back"
        },
        {
          "name": "Add Reverse"
        }
      ],
      "cards": [
        {
          "name": "Card 1",
          "front": "{{Front}}",
          "back": "{{FrontSide}}<hr>{{Back}}"
        },
        {
          "name": "Card 2",
          "front": "{{#Add Reverse}}{{Back}}{{/Add Reverse}}",
          "back": "{{FrontSide}}<hr>{{Front}}"
        }
      ],
      "styles": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 1607392322,
      "name": "Basic (type in the answer)",
      "cloze": false,
      "fields": [
        {
          "name": "Front"
        },
        {
          "name": "Back"
        }
      ],
      "cards": [
        {
          "name": "Card 1",
          "front": "{{Front}}<br>{{type:Back}}",
          "back": "{{Front}}<hr>{{Back}}"
        }
      ],
      "styles": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 1607392323,
      "name": "Cloze",
      "cloze": true,
      "fields": [
        {
          "name": "Text"
        },
        {
          "name": "Back Extra"
        }
      ],
      "cards": [
        {
          "name": "Cloze",
          "front": "{{cloze:Text}}",
          "back": "{{cloze:Text}}<br>{{Back Extra}}"
        }
      ],
      "styles": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 7702450,
      "name": "Basic Math",
      "cloze": false,
      "fields": [
        {
          "name": "Front"
        },
        {
          "name": "Back"
        },
        {
          "name": "Related"
        },
        {
          "name": "Extra"
        }
      ],
      "cards": [
        {
          "name": "Card 1",
          "front": "<div class=\"front\">{{Front}}</div>",
          "back": "{{FrontSide}}\n<hr>\n<div class=\"back\">\n  {{Back}}\n\n  {{#Related}}\n    <p class=\"sub\">Related</p>\n    {{Related}}\n  {{/Related}}\n\n  {{#Extra}}\n    <p class=\"sub\">Extra</p>\n    {{Extra}}\n  {{/Extra}}\n</div>"
        }
      ],
      "styles": "@media (min-width: 600px) {\n  .card {\n    max-width: 40rem;\n    margin: 1rem auto;\n    padding: 1rem;\n    border: 1px solid gray;\n    box-shadow: 0 10px 15px rgba(0,0,0,0.1);\n  }\n}\n.front {\n  text-align: center;\n}\n.back {\n  text-align: start;\n}\n.sub {\n  font-weight: bold;\n  color: gray;\n  border-bottom: 1px solid gray;\n}"
    },
    {
      "id": 7702451,
      "name": "Basic Math (and reversed card)",
      "cloze": false,
      "fields": [
        {
          "name": "Front"
        },
        {
          "name": "Back"
        },
        {
          "name": "Related"
        },
        {
          "name": "Extra"
        }
      ],
      "cards": [
        {
          "name": "Card 1",
          "front": "<div class=\"front\">{{Front}}</div>",
          "back": "{{FrontSide}}\n<hr>\n<div class=\"back\">\n  {{Back}}\n\n  {{#Related}}\n    <p class=\"sub\">Related</p>\n    {{Related}}\n  {{/Related}}\n\n  {{#Extra}}\n    <p class=\"sub\">Extra</p>\n    {{Extra}}\n  {{/Extra}}\n</div>"
        },
        {
          "name": "Card 2",
          "front": "<div class=\"front\">{{Back}}</div>",
          "back": "{{FrontSide}}\n<hr>\n<div class=\"back\">\n  {{Front}}\n\n  {{#Related}}\n    <p class=\"sub\">Related</p>\n    {{Related}}\n  {{/Related}}\n\n  {{#Extra}}\n    <p class=\"sub\">Extra</p>\n    {{Extra}}\n  {{/Extra}}\n</div>"
        }
      ],
      "styles": "@media (min-width: 600px) {\n  .card {\n    max-width: 40rem;\n    margin: 1rem auto;\n    padding: 1rem;\n    border: 1px solid gray;\n    box-shadow: 0 10px 15px rgba(0,0,0,0.1);\n  }\n}\n.front {\n  text-align: center;\n}\n.back {\n  text-align: start;\n}\n.sub {\n  font-weight: bold;\n  color: gray;\n  border-bottom: 1px solid gray;\n}"
    }
  ],
  "notes": [
    {
      "guid": "tsjqWGG2sy",
      "type": "Cloze",
      "deck": "Geography",
      "tags": [
        "Geography",
        "Capital"
      ],
      "fields": {
        "Text": "<p>The capital of {{c1::Mongolia::country}} is {{c2::Ulaanbaatar::city}}.</p>",
        "Back Extra": ""
      }
    },
    {
      "guid": "9cRqecNmPe",
      "type": "Cloze",
      "deck": "Geography",
      "tags": [
        "Geography",
        "Capital"
      ],
      "fields": {
        "Text": "<p>The capital of {{c1::Syria::country}} is {{c2::Damascus::city}}.</p>",
        "Back Extra": ""
      }
    },
    {
      "guid": "PjHgZNbLbL",
      "type": "Basic",
      "deck": "Math",
      "tags": [
        "Math",
        "Equation"
      ],
      "fields": {
        "Front": "<p>Quadratic Formula</p>",
        "Back": "\\[ x = \\frac{-b \\pm \\sqrt{b^2 - 4ac}}{2a} \\]"
      }
    },
    {
      "guid": "tfFUmGwnVe",
      "type": "Basic",
      "deck": "Math",
      "tags": [
        "Math",
        "Equation"
      ],
      "fields": {
        "Front": "<p>Euler&#39;s Formula</p>",
        "Back": "\\[ \\begin{align*}\n    e^{ix}  &= \\cos x + i \\sin x \\\\\n    e^{-ix} &= \\cos x - i \\sin x\n\\end{align*} \\]"
      }
    },
    {
      "guid": "8x5YMmQyYQ",
      "type": "Basic",
      "deck": "Math",
      "tags": [
        "Math",
        "Definition"
      ],
      "fields": {
        "Front": "<p>Mean Value Theorem</p>",
        "Back": "<p>The <strong>Mean Value Theorem</strong> states that if a function \\( f \\) is continuous on the closed interval \\( [a, b] \\) and differentiable on the open interval \\( (a, b) \\), then there exists at least one \\( c \\in (a, b) \\) such that</p>\n\\[ f'(c) = \\frac{f(b) - f(a)}{b - a} \\]"
      }
    }
  ]
}